smiley360.com 2012-12-17

# smiley360.com—Be Heard. Be Happy.

## smiley360.com Privacy Policy

smiley360.com ("we" or "us") recognizes the importance of respecting the privacy of those who visit this web site. Our web site makes it easy to share information with your friends and people around you. This Privacy Policy describes how we collect and use your information and gives you choices as to how we use it. We suggest that you review this Privacy Policy periodically as we may update it from time to time. This Privacy Policy was last revised on November 12, 2009.

### Privacy & Public Profile

At present, a PUBLIC PROFILE page exists, but is reserved for future use. smiley360.com does not allow you to share any profile information except your USERNAME at the smiley360.com web site. You choose what information you put in your public profile, and it is not required to use the web site.

### Safe Use of smiley360.com

smiley360.com wants to provide a site where people can interact safely with their friends and the people around them. To that end, smiley360.com has safety and privacy controls to ensure that users share information only with those they wish to.   
We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 13 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for smiley360.com or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on smiley360.com. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [member.support@smiley360.com](mailto:member.support@smiley360.com)  
In addition, parents of children 13 years and older should consider whether their child should be supervised during the child's use of our site. We recommend that minors 13 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet.  
Despite our best efforts to ensure a safe site, we cannot guarantee that the site is entirely free of illegal, offensive, pornographic or otherwise inappropriate material, or that its members will not encounter inappropriate or illegal conduct from other members. Consequently, you may encounter such content and conduct. You can help us by notifying us of any nudity, pornography, harassment or unwelcome contact by clicking on the "Report" link located on pages throughout the site. We will use our best efforts to review reports made through this site reporting tool within 24 hours and remove any content that is deemed to have violated the Terms of Service. If warranted we will also disable the access of the user responsible for posting the abusive content. Where complaints about nudity, pornography, harassment or unwelcome contact are made by independent email to [member.support@smiley360.com](mailto:member.support@smiley360.com) , we will acknowledge receipt of the complaint and begin to address it within 24 hours. We will respond to the reporter within 72 hours of receiving the email complaint to inform them of the steps we have taken to address it.  
[Click here](mailto:member.support@smiley360.com) to contact us regarding our handling procedures. Please note that if you have not previously made a complaint to us you should not use this link. We are solely responsible for complaint handling, and you should address all complaints or reports of abuse directly to us using the procedures described on this page.

### What do we collect

Every time you visit our Web site, our Web server automatically collects the following non-personally identifiable information: your Internet service provider's address, the referring URL and, information on the pages you access on our site.  
We also collect personally identifiable information that you provide, such as information you provide when you register on our site, for example, your name, your email address, your telephone number, your address, your gender, schools attended and any other personal or preference information that you provide to us.  
When you use our site, you may set up your personal profile, form relationships, send messages, perform searches and queries, form groups, set up events, add applications, and transmit information through various channels. We collect this information so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your friend list. When you update information, we usually keep a backup copy of the prior version for a reasonable period of time to enable reversion to the prior version of that information.  
We may also collect information about you from other sources, such as newspapers, blogs, instant messaging services, and other users of our service through the operation of the service in order to provide you with more useful information and a more personalized experience.  
By using the smiley360.com web site, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in the United States.

### What Are Cookies

Most Internet sites, including ours, collect data about visitors through the use of "cookies". Cookies are small software programs that help sites recognize repeat visitors by assigning a random number to each desktop for tracking content preferences and traffic patterns. Cookies may be used to "connect" your computer to information stored in a separate location. At the smiley360.com web site, we use cookies to connect your computer with the information we store for you in our database. Some examples of this information include items added to your shopping cart and user specific information on pages accessed and previous visits to our site. Your information is stored in a safe and secure database. Through cookies we may also: alert you to new products that we think might be of interest to you when you return to our site; record past activity at our site in order to provide you better service when you return to our site; or, customize Web page content based on your browser type or other information that you send us.  
We do not use cookies to store any of your personal or financial information on your computer.   
To learn more about how to set your browser to accept cookies, [Click here](javascript:newwindow\('cookie_popup.asp'\)). 

**How Do We Use Your Information?**  
When you register with smiley360.com, you create your own profile and privacy settings. Your profile information, as well as your name, email and photo, are displayed to people in the networks specified in your privacy settings to enable you to connect with people on smiley360.com. Profile information is used by smiley360.com primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to others permitted to view that information by your privacy settings. In some cases where your privacy settings permit it, other smiley360.com users may be able to supplement your profile.  
Profile information you submit to smiley360.com will be available to users of smiley360.com who belong to at least one of the networks you allow to access the information through your privacy settings (e.g., school, geography, friends of friends). Your name, network names, and profile picture thumbnail will be available in search results across the smiley360.com network and those limited pieces of information may be made available to third party search engines. This is primarily so your friends can find you and send a friend request. People who see your name in searches, however, will not be able to access your profile information unless they have a relationship to you (friend, friend of friend, member of your networks, etc.) that allows such access based on your privacy settings.  
We may use information about you that we collect from other sources, including but not limited to newspapers and Internet sources such as blogs and instant messaging services, to supplement your profile. Where such information is used, we will allow you to specify in your privacy settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connection of this information to your profile.  
We may use information in your profile without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people in a network like certain products and personalizing advertisements and promotions.   
Additionally, the information we collect is used: 

  * to generally improve the content and layout of our Web site 
  * to improve the content and layout of our Web site for individual visitors 
  * to notify you about updates to our Web site 
  * to contact you for marketing purposes 
  * for internal review 

When you supply us with personal information, and indicate your consent to receive promotional information, the information you provide will be added to our customer file. You may receive periodic mailings from us. If you do not want to receive such mailings from us, then please email us for information on where to contact us to remove yourself from our contact list.  
We may send you e-mail with information on new products. If you do not wish to receive such e-mail in the future, please email us for information on where to contact us to remove yourself from our e-mail list. We reserve the right to send you notices about your account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications.  
We may also send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. For instance, if someone in your network sends you a new message you may receive an email alerting you to that fact.

## Sharing Your Information with Third Parties

Our site and your privacy settings allow you to make informed choices about who has access to your information. We do not provide contact information to third party marketers without your permission. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is 1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, 2) legally required or, 3) permitted by you.   
In the event that there is a change in control of smiley360.com or, if all, or substantially all, of the assets of smiley360.com are sold to a third party, we may transfer the information on our customer file to the third party. This information may include your name, mailing address and email address among other information. Please know that if such a transfer takes place, the third party acquiring the information will be advised of your preferences about how we use your information. After the transfer takes place, use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy of the third party that acquires it. The acquiring company may continue to operate the smiley360.com website, if so, you should check this Privacy Policy periodically to determine how the acquiring entity will use your information.   
We may share information with governmental agencies or other companies assisting us in fraud prevention or investigation. We may do so when: (1) permitted or required by law; or, (2) trying to protect against or prevent actual or potential fraud or unauthorized transactions; or, (3) investigating fraud which has already taken place. The information is not provided to these companies for marketing purposes.   
When you use our site, certain information you post or share with third parties (e.g., a friend or someone in your network), such as personal information, comments, messages, photos, videos, listings or other information, may be shared with other users in accordance with the privacy settings you select. All such sharing of information is done at your own risk. Please keep in mind that if you disclose personal information in your profile or when posting comments, messages, photos, videos, listings or other items, this information may become publicly available.

## Links

Our site may contain links to other websites. We are of course not responsible for the privacy practices of other web sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by smiley360.com.

## Third Party Advertising

Third parties advertise on our site. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and "web beacons" (also known as "1x1 gifs") to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. smiley360.com does not have access to or control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on smiley360.com unless you choose to share it with them.  
This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by smiley360.com iand does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

**How can you update your information?**  
We will provide you access to the following information:

  * financial information (such as credit card account information) 
  * unique identifier information (customer number or password) 
  * transaction information (dates on which you made purchases, amounts and types of purchases) 
  * contact information (name, address, phone number) 

We will evaluate each request and reply in an appropriate manner and form of communication that ensures the security of the information you have requested.

**How do you know your information is secure?**  
When you see either a solid key icon or a locked padlock icon at the lower portion of your browser window, then your site is secured through Secure Sockets Layer. We use industry-standard encryption technologies when transferring and receiving your information on our site. If you do not see one of these icons, please contact your Internet service provider. When we transfer and receive certain types of sensitive information such as financial information, we will redirect you to a secure server and notify you through a pop-up screen on our site.   
We have appropriate security measures in place in our facilities to protect against the loss, misuse or alteration of information that we have collected from you at our site so you can feel comfortable and secure. 

Please note that e-mail is not encrypted and is not considered a secure means of transmitting credit card numbers. 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy Statement**  
From time to time, we may use the information you provide us for new, unanticipated uses not previously addressed in our Privacy Policy. If our information practices change at some time in the future we will post the policy changes on the privacy page of our Web site to notify you of these changes. You should check our Web site periodically for more information on how we use the data we collect.  
If there is a material change in the manner we use data we collect, we will update this Privacy Policy to reflect these changes. 

**Conflict In Terms**  
It is our goal to make our privacy practices easy to understand. We have created this easy-to-read Privacy Policy with that goal in mind. Some browsers utilize privacy enhancing technology to translate our Privacy Policy into a computer readable format and then translate it back into human readable format for you to read. This translation back into human readable format is often referred to as a "Policy Summary". To the extent that this Policy Summary is inconsistent with, fails to address or addresses an issue not raised in, our Privacy Policy, you should rely on our Privacy Policy as it is the controlling authority.

**Contact Us**  
To contact us for any reason, including a request to be added or taken off a list, or if you have any concerns or questions, please Click here. Please note: When you contact us, provide your name and address exactly as it appears on correspondence you have received from us.   
[Email us ](mailto:member.support@smiley360.com) to change your e-mail address or to unsubscribe from smiley360.com e-mail.  
If you feel that this site is not following its stated information privacy policy, you may contact us at the above address(es) or phone number or email address.

**Governing Law**

This privacy policy is governed by the laws of the State of New Jersey, without regard to its choice of law rule and without regard to the location of any user. Any dispute arising in connection with this policy must be filed in the state or federal courts located in New Jersey. 

**Change in Policy**

We reserve the right to revise, amend, change or update this privacy policy. For significant changes to this policy, we will notify you either by placing a prominent notice on the home page of our site or by sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this policy periodically to stay informed about our use of the information we collect. We will indicate near the top of this page the date this policy was last revised. Your continued use of the site after we have revised this policy constitutes your agreement to the revised version.
